STORE = [
  {
    question: "Who are the only two characters who appear in every Star Wars movie?",
    answers: [
      "Han and Chewbacca", "Darth Vader and Emperor Palpatine", "R2-D2 and C-3PO", "Luke and Leia"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "R2-D2 and C-3PO",
    trivia: "The first Star Wars movie  R2-D2 and C-3PO do not appear in is Solo. they even have cameos in many non-Star Wars films"
  },
  {
    question: "In which movie does Luke find out Darth Vader is his father?",
    answers: [
      "A New Hope", "Return of the Jedi", "Empire Strikes Back", "Attack of the Clones"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Empire Strikes Back",
    trivia: 'Darth Vader never actually says “Luke, I am your father.” He actually says, “No, I am your father.”'
  },
  {
    question: "What is Kylo Ren’s real name?",
    answers: [
      "Ben Solo","Han Solo","Rey Solo","Luke Solo"],
    correctAnswer: "Ben Solo",
    trivia: "Ben Solo is the son of Leia Organa and Han Solo, renaming himself Kylo Ren after turning to the dark side of the Force."
  },
  {
    question: "Who built C-3PO?",
    answers: [
      "Obi Wan Kenobi", "Rey", "Luke Skywalker", "Anakin Skywalker"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Anakin Skywalker",
    trivia: "When we first meet a young Anakin Skywalker on Tatooine, he excitedly shows off an unfinished droid, he calls '3PO' to Padme."
  },
  {
    question: "Who killed Qui-Gon Jinn?",
    answers: [
      "Darth Sidious", "Anakin Skywalker", "Jango Fett", "Darth Maul"],
    correctAnswer: "Darth Maul",
    trivia: "Darth Maul kills Qui-Gon Jinn while Obi One Kenobi is trapped behind a forcefield and unable to help."
  },
  {
    question: "Who inherits Han Solo’s ship?",
    answers: ["Finn","Poe Dameron","Rey","Chewbacca"],
    correctAnswer: "Rey",
    trivia: "After Han Solo’s death, Chewbacca recognizes Rey as the rightful heir to the ship."
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Luke and Leia’s mother?",
    answers: [
      "Breha Organa", "Beru Lars", "Cade Skywalker", "Padmé Amidala"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Padmé Amidala",
    trivia: "Luke and Leia finally find out they are twins in Return of the Jedi, when it is revealed that they were separated at birth."
  },
  {
    question: "What is Luke Skywalker’s homeworld?",
    answers: [
      "Tatooine", "Hoth", "Jakku", "Naboo"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Tatooine",
    trivia: "Obi Wan Kenobi ironically hid Luke on Tatooine, Anakin's home planet, to keep him safe from Darth Vader."
  },
  {
    question: "What position does Padmé Amidala hold following her term as Queen of Naboo?",
    answers: [
      "President of the Trade Federation", "Senator", "Sith Lord", "Supreme Chancellor"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Senator",
    trivia: "As a senator Padme oversaw the last few years of the Galactic Republic before the Empire took control."
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Princess Leia’s only hope?",
    answers: [
      "Luke Skywalker", "Obi Wan Kenobi", "R2 D2", "Han Solo"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Obi Wan Kenobi",
    trivia: "As one of the few remaining Jedi, and the watcher of Luke, Leia was always told her to contact Obi One on Tatooine, if her troubles ever became desperate."
  }

];
